A Finding Aid to the Cranmer Art Group Records, circa 1980-2021, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Client Files, 1980-2021; Series 1; Archival Resource Key; 55.2 Linear feet Boxes 1-54, 75
  - Client Files, 2011, K, Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Client Files, 2011, L, Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 7-8)
  - Client Files, 2011, Lennon Weinberg, Inc. (Joan Mitchell), Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Client Files, 2011, Estate of Roy Lichtenstein, Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Client Files, 2011, M, Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 11-12)
  - Client Files, 2011, Matthew Marks Gallery, Archival Resource Key; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD). (Box 37, Folder 13-14)
  - Client Files, 2011, N-O, Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Client Files, 2011, Joy Newman, Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Client Files, 2011, Nick Nicholas, Jr. (Richard Diebenkorn), Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Client Files, 2011, P, Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Client Files, 2011, Evelyn Pousette-Dart (Richard Pousette-Dart), Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 19-20)
  - Client Files, 2011, R, Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Client Files, 2011, Robert Rauschenberg, Inc., Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Client Files, 2011, Eric Rudin (Roy Lichtenstein), Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Client Files, 2011, S, Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 24-25)
  - Client Files, 2011, Richard Serra Studio, Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - Client Files, 2011, The Shidler Group, Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - Client Files, 2011, T-V, Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 28)
  - Client Files, 2011, W-Z, Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 29)
  - Client Files, 2012, A, Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 30-31)
  - Client Files, 2012, B, Archival Resource Key (Box 37, Folder 32)
  - Client Files, 2012, C, Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Client Files, 2012, Christie's, Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 2-3)
  - Client Files, 2012, Paula Cooper Gallery, Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Client Files, 2012, D, Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Client Files, 2012, Johanna Liesbeth de Kooning Trust (Willem de Kooning), Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Client Files, 2012, E, Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Client Files, 2012, F, Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 8-9)
  - Client Files, 2012, G, Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Client Files, 2012, Gagosian Gallery, Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Client Files, 2012, H, Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 12-13)
  - Client Files, 2012, Mary Heilmann, Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Client Files, 2012, Harmon Fine Arts, Inc., Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Client Files, 2012, I-K, Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Client Files, 2012, JBBO, LLC (Jo Baer), Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 17-18)
  - Client Files, 2012, L, Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 19-21)
  - Client Files, 2012, Estate of Roy Lichtenstein, Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Client Files, 2012, L & M Arts, 2011-2012; Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 23-24)
  - Client Files, 2012, M, Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 25-26)
  - Client Files, 2012, David Marden (Brice Marden), Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - Client Files, 2012, Metro Pictures (Robert Longo), Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - Client Files, 2012, Matthew Marks Gallery, Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 29-30)
  - Client Files, 2012, N-P, Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 31)
  - Client Files, 2012, R, Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 32)
  - Client Files, 2012, Mitchell P. Rales (Ellsworth Kelly), Archival Resource Key (Box 38, Folder 33)
  - Client Files, 2012, S, Archival Resource Key (Box 39, Folder 1-4)
  - Client Files, 2012, T-Z, Archival Resource Key (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Client Files, 2013, A-B, Archival Resource Key (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Client Files, 2013, C-F, Archival Resource Key (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Client Files, 2013, Christie's, Archival Resource Key (Box 39, Folder 8-9)
  - Client Files, 2013, Willem de Kooning Foundation, Archival Resource Key (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Client Files, 2013, G, Archival Resource Key (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Client Files, 2013, Gagosian Gallery, Archival Resource Key (Box 39, Folder 12-13)
  - Client Files, 2013, H, Archival Resource Key (Box 39, Folder 14-15)
  - Client Files, 2013, Haunch of Venison, New York, Archival Resource Key (Box 39, Folder 16-17)
  - Client Files, 2013, Mary Heilmann, Archival Resource Key (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Client Files, 2013, Marlene Hess and Jim Zirin, Archival Resource Key (Box 39, Folder 19-20)
  - Client Files, 2013, J-K, Archival Resource Key (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Client Files, 2013, Tom Jaffe, 2012-2013; Archival Resource Key (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Client Files, 2013, Michael Kohn Gallery, Archival Resource Key (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - Client Files, 2013, L, Archival Resource Key (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - Client Files, 2013, Estate of Roy Lichtenstein, Archival Resource Key (Box 39, Folder 25-26)
  - Client Files, 2013, Luxembourg & Dayan, Archival Resource Key (Box 39, Folder 27)
  - Client Files, 2013, M, Archival Resource Key (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Client Files, 2013, Matthew Marks Gallery (Ellsworth Kelly), Archival Resource Key (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Client Files, 2013, Mnuchin Gallery, Archival Resource Key (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Client Files, 2013, Rodman W. Moorhead III (Helen Frankenthaler), Archival Resource Key (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Client Files, 2013, N-P, Archival Resource Key (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Client Files, 2013, R, Archival Resource Key (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Client Files, 2013, Robert Rauschenberg Foundation, Archival Resource Key (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Client Files, 2013, S, Archival Resource Key (Box 40, Folder 8-9)
  - Client Files, 2013, Allison Sarofim (Agnes Martin), Archival Resource Key (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Client Files, 2013, The Shidler Group, Archival Resource Key (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Client Files, 2013, T-V, Archival Resource Key (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Client Files, 2013, Van Doren Waxter, Archival Resource Key (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Client Files, 2013, W-X, Archival Resource Key (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Client Files, 2013, David Zwirner Gallery, Archival Resource Key (Box 40, Folder 15-17)
  - Client Files, 2014, A, Archival Resource Key (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Client Files, 2014, Art Institute of Chicago (Christopher Wool), Archival Resource Key (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Client Files, 2014, B, Archival Resource Key (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Client Files, 2014, Bettina Sulser Bryant (Ellsworth Kelly), Archival Resource Key (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Client Files, 2014, Christie's, Archival Resource Key (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Client Files, 2014, Cincinnati Art Museum (Ellsworth Kelly), Archival Resource Key (Box 40, Folder 23)
  - Client Files, 2014, D-E, Archival Resource Key (Box 40, Folder 24)
  - Client Files, 2014, Willem de Kooning Foundation, Archival Resource Key (Box 40, Folder 25)
  - Client Files, 2014, F-G, Archival Resource Key (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - Client Files, 2014, Gagosian Gallery, Archival Resource Key (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Client Files, 2014, Gagosian Gallery (Marcel Duchamp), Archival Resource Key (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Client Files, 2014, H, Archival Resource Key (Box 41, Folder 3-4)
  - Client Files, 2014, Mary Heilmann, Archival Resource Key (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Client Files, 2014, J, Archival Resource Key (Box 41, Folder 6-7)
  - Client Files, 2014, JBBO, LLC, Archival Resource Key (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Client Files, 2014, Jack Kirkland (Ad Reinhardt), Archival Resource Key (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Client Files, 2014, K, Archival Resource Key (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Client Files, 2014, L, Archival Resource Key (Box 41, Folder 11-13)
  - Client Files, 2014, Luxembourg & Dayan, Archival Resource Key (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Client Files, 2014, M, Archival Resource Key (Box 41, Folder 15-16)
  - Client Files, 2014, Matthew Marks Gallery (Ellsworth Kelly), Archival Resource Key (Box 41, Folder 17-18)
  - Client Files, 2014, N-P, Archival Resource Key (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Client Files, 2014, Valentina Pero, Archival Resource Key (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Client Files, 2014, R, Archival Resource Key (Box 41, Folder 21-22)
  - Client Files, 2014, Robert Rauschenberg Foundation, Archival Resource Key (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - Client Files, 2014, Andrea Rosen Gallery, Archival Resource Key (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - Client Files, 2014, Richard Rush (Roy Lichtenstein), Archival Resource Key (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Client Files, 2014, S, Archival Resource Key (Box 41, Folder 26-28)
  - Client Files, 2014, The Shidler Group, Archival Resource Key (Box 41, Folder 29)
  - Client Files, 2014, Sotheby's, Archival Resource Key (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Client Files, 2014, T, Archival Resource Key (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Client Files, 2014, TishmanSpeyer Properties, Archival Resource Key (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Client Files, 2014, UBS Art Collection, Archival Resource Key (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Client Files, 2014, Untitled Press, Inc. (Robert Rauschenberg), Archival Resource Key (Box 42, Folder 5-6)
  - Client Files, 2014, V, Archival Resource Key (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Client Files, 2014, W, Archival Resource Key (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Client Files, 2014, David Zwirner Gallery, Inc., Archival Resource Key (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Client Files, 2015, A, Archival Resource Key (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Client Files, 2015, B-C, Archival Resource Key (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Client Files, 2015, D, Archival Resource Key (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Client Files, 2015, Willem de Kooning Foundation, Archival Resource Key (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Client Files, 2015, E, Archival Resource Key (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Client Files, 2015, F, Archival Resource Key (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Client Files, 2015, G, Archival Resource Key (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Client Files, 2015, Gagosian Gallery, Archival Resource Key (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Client Files, 2015, H-J, Archival Resource Key (Box 42, Folder 18-19)
  - Client Files, 2015, JBBO, LLC, Archival Resource Key (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Client Files, 2015, K, Archival Resource Key (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Client Files, 2015, L, Archival Resource Key (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Client Files, 2015, Luxembourg & Dayan, Archival Resource Key (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Client Files, 2015, M, Archival Resource Key (Box 42, Folder 24-25)
  - Client Files, 2015, Mnuchin Gallery, Archival Resource Key (Box 42, Folder 26)
  - Client Files, 2015, Thordis Moeller, Inc. (Blinky Palermo), Archival Resource Key (Box 43, Folder 1-2)
  - Client Files, 2015, N-O, Archival Resource Key (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Client Files, 2015, Stephen Ongpin Fine Art, Archival Resource Key (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Client Files, 2015, P, Archival Resource Key (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Client Files, 2015, R, Archival Resource Key (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Client Files, 2015, The Rachofsky Collection (Jo Baer), Archival Resource Key (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Client Files, 2015, S, Archival Resource Key (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Client Files, 2015, Sheri and Howard Schultz, Archival Resource Key (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Client Files, 2015, Richard Serra Studio, Archival Resource Key (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Client Files, 2015, Sotheby's, Archival Resource Key (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Client Files, 2015, T-U, Archival Resource Key (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Client Files, 2015, UBS Art Collection, Archival Resource Key (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Client Files, 2015, V-Z, Archival Resource Key (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Client Files, 2015, Michael Werner Gallery, Archival Resource Key (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Client Files, 2015, Christopher Wool, Archival Resource Key (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - 2016 Delivery and Stretcher Invoices, Archival Resource Key (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Client Files, 2016, A, Archival Resource Key (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Client Files, 2016, Anne Abbott (Andy Warhol), Archival Resource Key (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Client Files, 2016, Albright-Knox Art Gallery (Gerhard Richter), Archival Resource Key (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Client Files, 2016, B, Archival Resource Key (Box 43, Folder 21-22)
  - Client Files, 2016, Broad Art Museum (Andrew Sendor), Archival Resource Key (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Client Files, 2016, C, Archival Resource Key (Box 43, Folder 24-25)
  - Client Files, 2016, Christie's, Archival Resource Key (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - Client Files, 2016, D-G, Archival Resource Key (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - Client Files, 2016, Willem de Kooning Foundation, Archival Resource Key (Box 43, Folder 28-29)
  - Client Files, 2016, H, Archival Resource Key (Box 43, Folder 30-31)
  - Client Files, 2016, Mary Heilmann, Archival Resource Key (Box 43, Folder 32)
  - Client Files, 2016, I-J, Archival Resource Key (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Client Files, 2016, K, Archival Resource Key (Box 44, Folder 2-3)
  - Client Files, 2016, Kayne Griffin Corcoran (Mary Heilmann), Archival Resource Key (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Client Files, 2016, L, Archival Resource Key (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Client Files, 2016, Luxembourg & Dayan, Archival Resource Key (Box 44, Folder 6-7)
  - Client Files, 2016, M, Archival Resource Key (Box 44, Folder 8-9)
  - Client Files, 2016, Bruno Mederios, Archival Resource Key (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Client Files, 2016, Metropolitan Museum of Art (Stuart Davis), Archival Resource Key (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Client Files, 2016, Mnuchin Gallery, Archival Resource Key (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Client Files, 2016, N-P, Archival Resource Key (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Client Files, 2016, National Gallery of Art (Yves Klein), Archival Resource Key (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Client Files, 2016, Stephen Ongpin Fine Art, Archival Resource Key (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Client Files, 2016, Phillips, Archival Resource Key (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Client Files, 2016, R, Archival Resource Key (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Client Files, 2016, S, Archival Resource Key (Box 44, Folder 18-21)
  - Client Files, 2016, Richard Serra Studio, Archival Resource Key (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - Client Files, 2016, T-U, Archival Resource Key (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - Client Files, 2016, David Teiger Trust (Richard Diebenkorn), Archival Resource Key (Box 44, Folder 24-25)
  - Client Files, 2016, UBS Art Collection, Archival Resource Key (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - Client Files, 2016, V, Archival Resource Key (Box 44, Folder 27)
  - Client Files, 2016, Van Doren Waxter, Archival Resource Key (Box 44, Folder 28-29)
  - Client Files, 2016, VMS LLC, Archival Resource Key (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Client Files, 2016, W-Z, Archival Resource Key (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Client Files, 2016, Michael Werner Gallery, Archival Resource Key (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - 2017 Delivery and Stretcher Invoices, Archival Resource Key (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Client Files, 2017, A, Archival Resource Key (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Client Files, 2017, Athena Art Finance Corporation, Archival Resource Key (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Client Files, 2017, AXA Art Americas Corp., Archival Resource Key (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Client Files, 2017, B, Archival Resource Key (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Client Files, 2017, Busan Biennale, Archival Resource Key (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Client Files, 2017, C-D, Archival Resource Key (Box 45, Folder 10-11)
  - Client Files, 2017, Christen Sveaas Art Collection (Sigmar Polke), Archival Resource Key (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Client Files, 2017, Christie's, Archival Resource Key (Box 45, Folder 13-14)
  - Client Files, 2017, E-F, Archival Resource Key (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Client Files, 2017, Ellen Arts Projects LLC, Archival Resource Key (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Client Files, 2017, Helen Frankenthaler Foundation, Archival Resource Key (Box 45, Folder 17-18)
  - Client Files, 2017, G-H, Archival Resource Key (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Client Files, 2017, Anthony Grant Inc., Archival Resource Key (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Client Files, 2017, Gagosian Gallery, Archival Resource Key (Box 45, Folder 21-22)
  - Client Files, 2017, J-K, Archival Resource Key (Box 45, Folder 23)
  - Client Files, 2017, Per Hanbro Jensen, Archival Resource Key (Box 45, Folder 24)
  - Client Files, 2017, L, Archival Resource Key (Box 45, Folder 25-26)
  - Client Files, 2017, Roy Lichtenstein Estate, Archival Resource Key (Box 45, Folder 27)
  - Client Files, 2017, Luxembourg & Dayan, Archival Resource Key (Box 45, Folder 28)
  - Client Files, 2017, M, Archival Resource Key (Box 45, Folder 29-30)
  - Client Files, 2017, Mnuchin Gallery, Archival Resource Key (Box 46, Folder 1-3)
  - Client Files, 2017, Stephen Ongpin Fine Art, Archival Resource Key (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Client Files, 2017, P, Archival Resource Key (Box 46, Folder 5-6)
  - Client Files, 2017, Jeffrey and Marsha Perelman (Franz Kline), Archival Resource Key (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Client Files, 2017, R, Archival Resource Key (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Client Files, 2017, Michael Rosenfeld Gallery, Archival Resource Key (Box 46, Folder 9-12)
  - Client Files, 2017, Eric Rudin, Archival Resource Key (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Client Files, 2017, S, Archival Resource Key (Box 46, Folder 14-15)
  - Client Files, 2017, Sotheby's, Archival Resource Key (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Client Files, 2017, Kristy Stubbs Gallery (Frank Stella), Archival Resource Key (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Client Files, 2017, T, Archival Resource Key (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - Client Files, 2017, V, Archival Resource Key (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - Client Files, 2017, VMS LLC, Archival Resource Key (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - Client Files, 2017, W, Archival Resource Key (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - Client Files, 2017, YK Family Art LLC (Yayoi Kusama), Archival Resource Key (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - Client Files, 2017, David Zwirner Gallery LLC, Archival Resource Key (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - 2018 Delivery and Stretcher Invoices, Archival Resource Key (Box 46, Folder 24)
  - Client Files, 2018, A, Archival Resource Key (Box 46, Folder 25)
  - Client Files, 2018, B, Archival Resource Key (Box 46, Folder 26)
  - Client Files, 2018, Derek Brown (Christopher Wool), Archival Resource Key (Box 46, Folder 27)
  - Client Files, 2018, C, Archival Resource Key (Box 46, Folder 28-29)
  - Client Files, 2018, Christie's, Archival Resource Key (Box 46, Folder 30)
  - Client Files, 2018, Christie's, Archival Resource Key (Box 47, Folder 1-2)
  - Client Files, 2018, Cowles Charitable Trust (Frank Stella), Archival Resource Key (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Client Files, 2018, Willem de Kooning Foundation, Archival Resource Key (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Client Files, 2018, Johanna Liesbeth de Kooning Trust, Archival Resource Key (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Client Files, 2018, E, Archival Resource Key (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Client Files, 2018, F-G, Archival Resource Key (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Client Files, 2018, Helen Frankenthaler Foundation, Archival Resource Key (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Client Files, 2018, Gagosian Gallery, Archival Resource Key (Box 47, Folder 9-10)
  - Client Files, 2018, Estate of Madeline Gins (Arakawa), Archival Resource Key (Box 47, Folder 11-12)
  - Client Files, 2018, H, Archival Resource Key (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Client Files, 2018, Mary Heilmann, Archival Resource Key (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Client Files, 2018, J. Tomilson Hill (Christopher Wool), Archival Resource Key (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Client Files, 2018, J-K, Archival Resource Key (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Client Files, 2018, Jedermann, Inc., Archival Resource Key (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Client Files, 2018, David Johnson, Archival Resource Key (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Client Files, 2018, L, Archival Resource Key (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Client Files, 2018, The Robert Lehrman Revocable Trust, Archival Resource Key (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - Client Files, 2018, Estate of Roy Lichtenstein, Archival Resource Key (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - Client Files, 2018, Lisson Gallery, Archival Resource Key (Box 47, Folder 22-23)
  - Client Files, 2018, Luhring Augustine Gallery, Archival Resource Key (Box 47, Folder 24)
  - Client Files, 2018, M, Archival Resource Key (Box 47, Folder 25-26)
  - Client Files, 2018, Mnuchin Gallery, Archival Resource Key (Box 47, Folder 27)
  - Client Files, 2018, N, Archival Resource Key (Box 47, Folder 28)
  - Client Files, 2018, Alf Naman Collection (Mary Heilmann), Archival Resource Key (Box 47, Folder 29)
  - Client Files, 2018, Stephen Ongpin Fine Art, Archival Resource Key (Box 48, Folder 1-2)
  - Client Files, 2018, P, Archival Resource Key (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Client Files, 2018, Phillips, Archival Resource Key (Box 48, Folder 4-5)
  - Client Files, 2018, Judith Pisar (Mark Rothko), Archival Resource Key (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Client Files, 2018, Stephen Posen, Archival Resource Key (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Client Files, 2018, R, Archival Resource Key (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Client Files, 2018, S, Archival Resource Key (Box 48, Folder 9-10)
  - Client Files, 2018, Julian Schnabel (Albert Oehlen), Archival Resource Key (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Client Files, 2018, The Shidler Group, Archival Resource Key (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Client Files, 2018, Sotheby's, Archival Resource Key (Box 48, Folder 13-14)
  - Client Files, 2018, Katherine A. Stahl (Le Corbusier), Archival Resource Key (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Client Files, 2018, T, Archival Resource Key (Box 48, Folder 16-18)
  - Client Files, 2018, Steven Tananbaum (Brice Marden), Archival Resource Key (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Client Files, 2018, U-V, Archival Resource Key (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - Client Files, 2018, UBS Art Collection, Archival Resource Key (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - Client Files, 2018, University of Arizona Museum of Art (Willem de Kooning), Archival Resource Key (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - Client Files, 2018, W-Z, Archival Resource Key (Box 48, Folder 23-24)
  - 2019 Delivery and Stretcher Invoices, Archival Resource Key (Box 48, Folder 25)
  - Client Files, 2019, A, Archival Resource Key (Box 48, Folder 26)
  - Client Files, 2019, Abstracts LLC (Mark Rothko), Archival Resource Key (Box 48, Folder 27)
  - Client Files, 2019, B, Archival Resource Key (Box 48, Folder 28)
  - Client Files, 2019, Roy Ben-Yami (Ellsworth Kelly), Archival Resource Key (Box 48, Folder 29)
  - Client Files, 2019, C, Archival Resource Key (Box 48, Folder 30-31)
  - Client Files, 2019, Christie's, Archival Resource Key (Box 49, Folder 1-3)
  - Client Files, 2019, Paula Cooper Gallery (David Novros), Archival Resource Key (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Client Files, 2019, Dia Art Foundation, Archival Resource Key (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Client Files, 2019, E-F, Archival Resource Key (Box 49, Folder 6-7)
  - Client Files, 2019, Helen Frankenthaler Foundation, Archival Resource Key (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Client Files, 2019, G, Archival Resource Key (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Client Files, 2019, Gagosian Gallery, Archival Resource Key (Box 49, Folder 10-12)
  - Client Files, 2019, Gfoeller Foundation (Pablo Picasso), Archival Resource Key (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Client Files, 2019, H, Archival Resource Key (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Client Files, 2019, Barbara Heizer (Michael Heizer), Archival Resource Key (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Client Files, 2019, J, Archival Resource Key (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - Client Files, 2019, L, Archival Resource Key (Box 49, Folder 17-18)
  - Client Files, 2019, Lisson Gallery, Archival Resource Key (Box 49, Folder 19-20)
  - Client Files, 2019, Luhring Augustine Gallery, Archival Resource Key (Box 49, Folder 21-22)
  - Client Files, 2019, M, Archival Resource Key (Box 49, Folder 23-24)
  - Client Files, 2019, Linda Macklowe, Archival Resource Key (Box 49, Folder 25)
  - Client Files, 2019, Mnuchin Gallery, Archival Resource Key (Box 49, Folder 26)